Daniel Pitt

✓ danielpitt1027@gmail.com

Male

Singapore, Singapore

https://join.skype.com/invite/FTt0mmHoS1V2

Profile

I am a passionate senior full stack engineer with over 10 years of experience in software engineering. Always love challenges and hard working to achieve goals. Have advanced knowledge of multiple programming languages, frameworks and extensive familiarity with several database structures.

Working as a senior developer, lead developer, I have built several successful websites, mobile apps, and DeFi platforms for a large number of users, and have successfully completed several projects involving various technical fields depending on the business idea of the client.

Education

2008/08 - 2011/12

Bachelor's Degree, Computer Software Engineering

National University of Singapore

Experience

2020/02 - present

Full-Stack Software Engineer

Self-Freelancing

Due to the pandemic, I had to transition to remote work, and I discovered that it was an exciting and efficient method of working. I thoroughly enjoyed the experience and found it to be highly productive. I always strive to build long-term professional relationships with my clients.

• Blockchain Development - https://dapp-prestaging.sundrip.io/ ☐ Making digital property on several blockchain networks.

2016/08 - 2020/10

Frontend Software Engineer

Sun Asterisk Inc

Working for this company was my golden period, I got many opportunities to develop extended web applications. I extended my skills larger to the frontend part based on backend experience and I started to approach full stack more easily.

What I tried to join to develop are as follows:

- https://whatsyourgusto.com/ □
- https://aliabdaal.com/articles/ ☑
- https://www.leifshop.com/ ☑
- https://debut.shonenmagazine.com/

2014/04 - 2016/07

Full-Stack Software Engineer

Sun Asterisk Inc

PHP/Laravel to Python/Django - https://infcurion.com/ ☑

Incurion is a website that provides platforms, consulting, etc. centered on the financial and payment fields. It provides various services, employment information, and news and inquiry.

2013/11 - 2014/02

Frontend Software Engineer Intern

Kisko

I spent over 1,000+ hours of intensive training where I have enhanced the skills to be an efficient Full Stack Developer, with a strong understanding of problem-solving, critical thinking, and software engineering that maintain, develop and deploy fully functional dynamic web/mobile application from scratch.

Skills

Web Frontend

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Vue, Angular, Next, Joint, Svelte

Mobile App Native

Android:Java, Kotlin, JetPack Compose, iOS:Swift/SwiftUI

Blockchain

Web3, Smart Contract, Solidity, Rust, Ethereum/EIP, Truffle, Hardhat, OpenZeppelin

DB, Cloud Services

MySQL, SQLite, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, GraphQL, Firebase, AWS, Google Maps, Amplify, Twilio, etc

Web Backend

PHP/Laravel, Python/Django&Flask, NodeJS/Express, Rust, C#/ASP.NET, Java/JSP

Mobile App Cross-Platform, Hybrid ● ● ●

Flutter, React Native, Xamarin

AI/ML • • • • •

Google ML kit, Numpy, MatplotLib, Keras, Pytorch, Scikit-learn

Windows/Linux Desktop App

C/C++/C#, QT/QML, PyQT